# **CHUNG EE LENG**

+6017-2073993 eeleng.chung@gmail.com Bukit Jalil, Kuala Lumpur



An agile thinker and detail-oriented individual with experience in managing day-to-day and backend operations. With a can-do attitude and willingness to learn, I am a dedicated and focused team player who excels at prioritising, completing multiple tasks simultaneously, and following through to achieve goals.

# **Work Experience**

04/2020 - 08/2022 August Store, Bangsar Village 2 & The Gardens Mall

## Operation Manager

- Manage all aspects of the stores and is responsible to lead team to achieve sales target
- Analyse and implement changes to process workflow and store layout to ensure safety and efficiency
- Resolve complaints and devise ways to improve issues related to complex customer service situations
- Recruit and train employees on product knowledge, operational and service skills
- Manage and appraise employees; plan staff work schedules between stores
- Responsible for all aspects of inventory management; monitor and deal with stock control
- Implement inter-store transfers and movement of stock to achieve optimal stock balances
- Propose and execute seasonal/quarterly product promotions to phase out older products as part of stock control process
- Work closely with the Buying Director to implement effective product selection within purchasing cycle
- Align purchase orders once stock arrives
- Handle all online channels
- Produce monthly sales reports, employees' payrolls

04/2019 - 03/2020 August Store, Bangsar Village 2

#### Operation Executive

- · Lead team to achieve store sales and profit target
- Resolve complaints and devise ways to improve issues revolving operations
- Manage and train employees

12/2018 - 02/2019 Grand Millennium Kuala Lumpur

## Human Resources Intern

- · Assist supervisors in completing tasks assigned
- Update and compile documents
- Create images and communications on company message to employees

2016 - 2019 August Store, BSC

### Sales Associate, Part-Time

- Achieve store sales and profit target
- Communicate product features clearly to customers' needs
- Perform store operations and complete cash register transactions accurately

### Education

08/2022 - Present General Assembly Software Engineering Immersive Course

03/2016 - 03/2019 Sunway University Bachelor of Science in International Hospitality Management First Class Honours

2013 - 2014 Sunway College

Monash University Foundation Year

## Languages

English - Native Mandarin - Advanced Cantonese - Fair Bahasa Melayu - Advanced

#### **Additional Skills**

- Problem-solving
- Effective Communication
- Time management
- Active learning
- Detail-oriented
- Proficient in MS Office (Word, Excel and Powerpoint), Shopify

#### References

Vivian Quah

Managing Director, August Store vivian@auguststoreofficial.com

Previna Mohanen

Asst Training Manager, Grand Millennium previna.mohanen@millenniumhotels.com